free-tv-video-online.info 2008-02-25

# Project Free TV - Privacy Policy

Project Free TV values your privacy. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information. We will never disclose your personal information (email address, etc.) and associated activity on this Web site to any third party, without your permission. 

**External Site Links and Embed Content**  

Project Free TV links to other websites on the internet. Content and Privacy Policies are the responsibility of their respective owners.

**IP Addresses and Logging**  

Project Free TV server logs information about visitors, including IP addresses, date/time visited, referring website, length of stay, etc. This information is used for site statistics only.

**Collection Of Personal Information**

Any information collected will not be shared or used for any purpose. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. None of the personal information collected will ever be shared with any third party company without consent from the user.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. Project Free TV does not use any cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Disclosure to third parties**

All the data that was transmitted to Project Free TV, will be treated confidentially! We will not distribute IP addresses or other information of visitors of this website to third parties.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting a notice on the home page of the Website.
